previously on Desperate Housewives
前情提要
I'm gonna die,
我就要死了
and I'd like to know what happened to my daughterbefore I do.
在那之前我想弄清我女儿 到底是怎么死的
When it comes to wisteria lane,
一提到紫藤街
there are old crimes...
旧案...
new crimes...
新案...
as soon as it gets dark,we get rid of that body.
天一黑  我们就把尸体处理掉
And crimes that are happening...
还有接二连三的事故...
right under everyone's nose.
就在所有人眼皮下
I'm thinkingit's the applewhites.
我猜是Applewhite一家
Jim halverson was aware that he had little to offer a woman.
Jim Halverson意识到 自己不怎么有女人缘
He was neither rich,nor smart,nor handsome.
他既不富有,也不睿智 更谈不上英俊
Are you jim?I'm susan mayer.
你是Jim么？ 我是Susan Mayer
So when his friend set him up on a blind date with a beautiful stranger...
所以每当他的朋友为他安排 和一个美丽的陌生女郎约会
wow,you're so much hotterthan nikki said you'd be.
你可比Nikki形容的性感多了
How old are you?
敢问芳龄？
How olddo you think I am?
你觉得呢？
Jim made the tragic decision to try to be funny.
Jim做了个悲哀的决定─ 试图表现幽默
Not a day over 50.
我猜没过50
why don't weget our table?
咱们去找张桌位吧
Well,no,see,that was funny,
呃..不是..我是开玩笑呢
because you'reso obviously not 50.
因为你显然没到50岁
That's why I said 50,'cause it's absurd.
所以我才说50 所以很荒谬
Jim did everything he could to get susan mayer to laugh.
Jim竭尽所能想博得佳人一笑
He tried racial humor...
他尝试了种族笑话
so guess what time chinesepeople go to the dentist?
猜猜中国人什么时候看牙医？
2:30.
2:30
uh,get it?"Tooth-hurty?"
明白了么？"tooth-hurty(牙疼)"
Tooth-hurty.
Tooth-hurty
I love that.
哈哈哈 逗死了
He tried to be engagingly risqu?..
他也试图有潇洒的来点黄笑话
rectum?Damn near killed him!
直肠？差点要了他的命啊
you know whata rectum is,right?
你知道直肠是什么吧？
he even tried gentle teasing.
他甚至尝试了温情的调戏
No,no,you see,by comparing you to a nazi,
不不不 看 之所以把你跟纳粹比较
I was making the pointthat you're so not a nazi.
我是想说你一点不像纳粹
thought the date couldn't get any worse....
就在Jim以为这次约会 糟糕透顶的时候
...It did.
还真的糟糕到“顶”了
Okay,jim,I need you to look up...
好了 Jim 现在往上看
and down.
往下
All right,so,how did this happen?
好了 这是怎么造成的
It was an accident.
是个小事故
Oh,I don't knowabout that.
哦 我不知道
In some cultureshead-butting is a mating ritual.
在某些文化里 顶脑门儿可是婚配仪式呢
Dr. Mccready,can italk to you about my head?
McCready医生 我能跟你谈谈我的头么
Away from...the draft?
咱们离仪器...远点儿
you can call medr. Ron. Everyone does.
你可以叫我Ron医生 大家都这么叫
dr. Ron...
Ron医生
I need you to pretendthere's something wrong with me and admit me for the night.
我需要你假装我病情严重 让我留院观察
I'm sorry?
什么？
This is the worst dateI have ever been on in my life.
这是我这辈子最糟的约会了
That man is the most obnoxious, offensive,annoying human being.
我没见过这么可恶，爱侮辱人， 又讨厌的人
And you're looking at melike I'm crazy right now,
你现在看着我好像我是个疯子
but I will be if I spendone more second with him.
但我要是跟他再多呆一秒钟 我真会疯的
So you gotta help me.You gotta do something.
你得帮帮我 帮我一把
It's my mental health.My mental health!
这关乎我的心理健康 心理健康啊
You took an oath.
你成为医生时可是发过誓的
Could you let goof my lapel,please?
你能别抓着我的领子么
Oh,sorry.
哦 对不起
Um,listen,I'm sorryyour date's not going well.
听我说 我很抱歉你得约会不成功
But I can'tadmit you,susan.
但我帮不了你,susan.
Right. Right.
好吧 好吧
Jim,let's,uh,let's takea look at those reflexes.
Jim 咱们来察察你的反射神经
Okay,I got a jokefor you,doctor.
好的,我有个小笑话,医生
What's the correct medical term for the circumcisionof a rabbit?
给兔子行割礼的医学术语是什么
Hare cut.
"Hare Cut" (兔割, 与理发同音)
I don't--I always--
哈哈我都...哈哈
jim,I'm gonna needto keep you here for awhile,run some tests.
Jim我的要求你留院观察 做些测试
Really? I--
真的么？ 我...
yeah,I'm still worried about that bump on your head here.
嗯,我很担心你的头上的肿块
That's still...
还是有点儿...
and,susan,
而..Susan
you're good to go.
你可以走了
And though it only lasted a moment,
虽然只是那么一瞬间
jim caught the look that passed between his date...
Jim还是捕捉到了他的约会对象和 医生之间的...
and his doctor.
眼神交会
Thank you so much,dr. Ron.
太谢谢你了 Ron医生
And he suddenly got the feeling
他突然感觉到..
the joke was on him.
他自己才是最可笑的笑话
www.ydy.com/bbs Proudly Presents
-=伊甸园美剧 http://sfile.ydy.com=- 荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
Sync: YTET-gagegao -==www.ydy.com/bbs==-
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=- 翻译: 午夜飞行  Carrie  七宝  Uuip  Noemie 校对: 午夜飞行  Uuip
Desperate Housewives Season 02 Episode 12
欢迎光临伊甸园美剧交流站 http://sfile.ydy.com
The annual blood drive was a tradition on wisteria lane.
年度献血活动是紫藤街的传统
Most residents came to help promote health and well-being,
大多数人来这里 为健康和善行贡献自己的力量
but my friends turned up for a different reason.
但我的朋友们的参与却另有原因
They were growing increasingly concerned
她们越来越担心
that their street was infected with a dangerous kind of sickness.
她们的街区上一种危险的疾病 开始蔓延了
And they came to consult with one another about a possible cure.
她们来这里协商 找出可行的处方
great, she caught me staring.
这下好了 她发现我盯着她们了
Have you guys noticed how friendly betty's been
你们注意到自从 在她家门前发现尸体后
since that body was found in front of her house?
她表现得特别友善么?
I don't trust friendly women.
我不信任友善的女人
That's okay. They don't trust you,either.
没事儿 她们也不信任你
I just know those two have something to do with that dead body.
我知道她们俩肯定和 那个尸体有关
Do we even know who he is?
那个人到底是谁啊?
Well,the paper said the police are withholding the details.
报纸说警方已经掌握了实情.
Bree,maybe you should call in a favor from your police detective pal,
Bree 或许你应该找 你的警官朋友帮帮忙
have him poke around.
让他打探打探
That's a great idea.
好主意.
You could have him do a background check on the applewhites.
你可以让他查查Applewhite母子的底细
I don't think I can do that.
我想我办不成.
Why not? You said he was nice.
为什么? 你说他人挺好的不是
Well,once he stopped suspecting me of murdering rex he was delightful,but,um...
自从他不再怀疑我谋杀rex以后 他是满友善的 但...
I don't really know him.
我跟他不怎么熟.
Well,somebody has to do something, 'cause I'm losing sleep.
得有个人做点什么 我现在都睡不着觉了.
Betty! Matthew.
Hello,everybody.
大家好啊.
Susan,a little birdie told me you're having a birthday soon.
Susan一只小鸟跟我呢喃细语. 说你要过生日了
We should all go out and celebrate.
我们应该一起出去庆祝一下.
Super.
太好啦.
Sounds like a plan.
我也参加.
Count me in.
算我一个
bye.
再见.
See ya.
回见.
So why are you everybody's best friend all of a sudden?
你怎么突然成了大伙的密友似的?
If there was ever a time to be neighborly,
如果应该表现得友善的话,
this is it.
现在是最合适的时机
We're idiots for staying here.
我们留在这儿太蠢了
I mean,we should've hit the road as soon as they found monroe's body.
他们发现Monroe的尸体的时候 我们就该跑路了
I mean,how do we know he didn't tell foster where we're hiding?
我们怎么知道他没告诉foster一家 我们藏在这儿?
Because if he had,foster would've shown up by now.
因为要是他说了 现在Foster家早有人来了
And besides,if we take off, what are we gonna live on?
况且 我们现在要是跑了 我们靠什么养活自己啊?
I have all of our money tied up in this house.
我们的钱全套在这座房子上了
So why not just sell it?
那干嘛不卖了?
Patience,matthew.
耐心点儿,Matthew
If we take off right away,
我们要是马上就走了
it'll look suspicious.
会让人起疑的
Now what we need is a story--
我们现在要编个故事--
a reason for us to move.
给我们一个搬走的理由
Look at this,a-b negative.
看啊, AB型RH阴性血
Yeah,it's the rarest of all blood types.
是啊,最难找的血型了
Well,there must be something in the water around these parts.
这附近的水一定有什么特殊成分
You're my second a-b negative today.
你是今天第二个AB型RH阴性血了
Seriously?
真的么?
Uh,who was it?
另一个是谁?
That guy.
那个人
Hi,bree.
嗨 Bree
Oh,hi.
噢 嗨
I just wanted to thank you for your advice on my azaleas.
我来谢谢你给 我的杜鹃花提的建议
They're just thriving.
它们长得好极了.
Oh,it was no trouble at all.
哦 这没什么的.
Such a shame I may not be around to enjoy them.
真遗憾我可能 留在这儿观赏它们了
Well,my mother has taken ill.
我母亲病了.
And matthew and I,
我和Matthew
we'll probably go and visit her.
我们可能要去看她.
We may even be moving.
我们甚至可能搬走了.
We just don't know yet.
还没定下来.
Oh,well, where does she live?
哦 是么 她住在哪儿?
Oh,back in chicago.
哦 芝加哥.
Is it serious?
病的严重么?
I-I don't know yet.
我..还不知道.
Well,obviously,I'll be speaking with her doctor.
很显然 我得和她的医生谈谈.
Oh,betty,if there's anything I can do, anything at all...
哦 Betty 要是有什么我能帮得上的 任何事...
thank you.
谢谢.
You've already done so much.
你帮得够多的了.
Bye.
再见.
That dr. Ron called.
那个Ron医生来电话了.
He needs to see you for a follow-up appointment.
他需要为你做个跟踪检查.
He needs to see me or he wants to see me?
他是“需要”还是“想要”?
Jeez,mom,how cute is this guy?
行了 妈 他到底有多帅?
Oh,he could be cuter...
噢 比他帅的人还是有的
but I don't know how.
但我还没遇见过.
So ask him out.
那约他出来啊.
Oh,no, I can't do that.
哦 不行 我不能.
Mom,he's a cute surgeon. What's the problem?
妈 他可是个帅哥外科医生 还有什么问题?
He's young.
他很年轻.
Young?
年轻？
Younger than me.
比我年轻.
How much younger?
有多年轻?
Let's just say if I was a senior in high school,
这么说吧 如果我是个高三学生
I'd be saying,"wow, you're a hot fifth grader."
我会说： "喔你真是个性感的五年级生"
Oh,well,of course it's gonna sound gross if you say it that way.
哦 当然你要是这么说就有点恶心了
But you're both adults.So why not just ask him out?
但你们都是成年人 干嘛不约他呢?
'Cause the conversation could go something like this,
因为我们的交谈会是这样：
"dr. Ron,I think you're hot."
"Ron医生 我觉得你很性感"
"Oh,well,thank you,ma'am.
"哦 谢谢你 太太"
"Now I think it's time we talk about your hip replacement."
"现在我们该谈谈如何换 你的髋关节"
Mom,you're hot
妈 你很性感
and funny and nice.
又幽默又善良
And... clearly desperate, and guys are into that.
而且...显然精力旺盛 男人喜欢这样的
Play to your strengths.
加油吧
Thank god you're home.
感谢上帝你终于回来了.
What's wrong? Pat said youtold her it was an emergency!
怎么了 Pat说你说很紧急!
The boys weresent home from school.
孩子们被学校送回来了.
What? Why? I called.The machine kept picking up.
什么？为什么？我打电话了 都转到了留言机
I know. I know.Look,I...
是啊 是啊 听我说 我...
they've got chicken pox.
他们起水痘了
Chicken pox?That's the emergency?
起水痘了？这就叫“紧急”?
They'retotally contagious.
他们很容易传染的.
Not to us.
又不传染我们.
They are to me!I've never had it.
能传染我！我没起过.
Well,you nevertold me that.
你从来没说过阿.
You know,the point is,I can't go in there.
问题是 我不能进屋.
It's a hot zone.
里面是传染区.
Well,tom,somebody'sgotta take care of our kids.
Tom 总要有人照顾孩子
Exactly.
对阿
And since you're immune--
既然你免疫了--
oh,you've gotta be kidding!I have to get back to work!
哦你开玩笑吧 我还得回去上班呢!
Just for a couple of days,until they're not contagious.
就几天 等到他们不传染了
It is not the ebola virus.It's chicken pox.
又不是埃博拉病毒 是水痘
You are being a baby.
别跟个小孩子似的.
Yes,I am.
说对了
Okay.
好吧
And if you thinkI'm being a baby now,
你要是以为我现在像个小孩子
do I need to remind youof what I'm like when I'm sick?
那你是否需要我提醒你 我病起来什么德行?
Remember that timeI had strep throat?
还记得我得浓毒性咽炎那次么?
We wound upin marriage counseling.
我们后来都去了婚姻咨询处.
I'll call the office.
我打电话给办公室.
Thanks,honey.
谢谢你 亲爱的.
Uh,mrs. Solis,I gotta talk to you.
Solis夫人 我得跟你谈谈.
Ralph,if this is about luis overwateringthe hydrangeas again,
Ralph 要是又关于 Luis给八仙花浇多了水
I told you, no one likes a tattletale.
我已经跟你说过了 没人喜欢打小报告的人.
My wife left me.
我妻子离开我了.
Oh,I'm sorry.
哦 真抱歉.
I didn't know you and bonitawere having problems.
我不知道你和Bonita之间有问题.
We weren't.
我们没什么问题.
Uh,it was all of a sudden. She just packed her bagsand left.
她就是突然 收拾行李走了.
She said I have an illness, and I need to get help.
她说我有病 说我需要帮助.
Why?
为什么?
There's nothingwrong with me.I just like to look atpretty ladies on the internet.
我没怎么 我只是喜欢上网看美女
And sure,they're not always dressed,
当然了 美女不总是穿着衣服,
and sometimes,there's more than one.
有时候 还不止一个人.
But I only go tothe classy web sites.
但我只去一些有档次的网站.
There's some really sick stuffout there, mrs. Solis.
网上有不少变态的东西 Solis太太
Ralph!
Make your point.
讲重点.
Um,last night,uh,I found this new web site.
昨晚 我去了个新的站点.
And there wasa picture of a lady sitting on a bearskin rug
一个女人坐在一张熊皮毯上
with nothing on except for a little pointyelf hat. It was very festive.
除了一个小矮人尖帽什么也没穿 挺喜庆的
Uh,ralph,why are youtelling me this?
Ralph 跟我说这个干嘛?
I'm sorry.It's just,um...
对不起 只是...
ahem. I think you reallyneed to see this.
我想你该看看这个.
Oh,my god!
哦 上帝啊!
The lighting looks greaton you,mrs. Solis.
灯光在你身上真好看 Solis太太
I mean,most of the time,you have to squint at the screen to see anything really good.
大多数时候 你必须斜视屏幕才能看到好东西
And not here,no,sir,that's good.
你这张却不用 不用 真棒
Well,um,thank you,ralph, for bringing thisto my attention.
啊..谢谢你 Ralph 谢谢你告诉我
Uh,mrs. Solis,I was wondering...
Solis太太 我在想
would you sign that for me?
你能给我在上面签个名么?
Oh,okay.
哦...好吧
where have you been?
你这段时间去哪儿了?
Why didn't you cometo see me?
怎么不来看我?
I came every sunday.
我每周日都来.
You were just too out of it to know I was here.
你只是头脑不清醒, 没意识到我来过.
I think you're lying.
我认为你在说谎.
But then again,these days, I think everyone'sbeen lying to me.
但是又说起这事, 这些天 我一直觉得每个人都在骗我
The thing is,you're here now.
不管怎么样, 你现在来了
So tell mewhat I wanna know.
那就说说我想知道的事情
Did you find the manwho killed my daughter?
你找到杀死我女儿的凶手了吗?
It was a guy namedtodd forrest--
是一个名叫todd forrest的家伙干的
this lowlife drug dealer.
他是一个落破的毒贩子
He got her hooked again.
再次诱骗了你女儿
She tried to steal from him,and he killed her.
她想偷他的东西, 结果被他杀了
And I killed him.
所以我就把他干掉了
I thought hearing thatwould make you happy.
我原以为这样会让你感到高兴的.
I thought it would,too.
我刚才也这样觉得
But it doesn't.
但是, 现在不是了
I'm sorry.
对不起.
I wanna start your I.V.,But your veins are kinda bad.
我是想给你输液 但是你的血管不太好扎
Well,here,let me help you.
好了, 我来帮帮你
What the hellare you doing?
你干什么?
You're crazy!
你疯了!
You're fired.Get out.
你被解雇了, 出去
So I guesswe're done then?
那我们之间的事情解决了?
Yeah.
是的
You,uh...
你...
you gonna come see me again?
你还会来看我吗?
You planning on havingan open casket?
除非到葬礼上开棺瞻仰的时候
Hey,guys.
嘿, 你们好
Hi,lynette.
你好, lynette
Hi,carlos.
你好, carlos
All right! A reuben?How sweet is that?
好了! 馅饼? 多周到
Lunch brought rightto the golf course.
送午餐到高尔夫球场来
I hear you got somepretty sick kids in there.
我听说你家里的孩子病的不轻
Oh,it's justchicken pox.
哦，就是出了点水痘
But braveheart here will onlycome in to sleep and shower.
可是这个勇敢男人 只敢进去睡个觉和冲个凉.
I can't say I blame him.
我不能说这是他的错
I wouldn't want to beshooting blanks either.
我也不想放空炮
Be well,my man,
保重, 兄弟
Bye,lynette.
再见, lynette
See you later.
回头见
I'm sorry,what did he mean,"shooting blanks"?
我不明白 他刚才说"放空炮"是什么意思?
Oh,it's nothing.
哦, 没什么
There's justa small chance
如果一个成年男子出了水痘
of sterility if a grown mangets chicken pox,so...
就有可能失去生殖能力 不过机率很小, 所以......
we're not having any more kids. Why would it matter?
我们都不准备再要孩子了 为什么还要担心这个?
I don't know.You know,survival instinct?
不知道. 也许是生存的本能吧
So that if you're the last manto survive a nuclear holocaust,
就是说如果 你成为一场核灾难的唯一幸存者
you could repopulatethe planet?
你会重新生育构建整个地球?
No,all I'm saying is that,
不是那意思, 我是说
god forbid something wereto happen to either one of us,
上帝会阻止一些事情发生在 你或我的身上
I'd want either one of usto have,you know,options.
我是想让你我中的任何一个人拥有这种 你知道的, 选择的权力
So you're sayingthat if I died...
那你是在说, 如果我去世了...
you would want a second wifeand a family?
你想娶第二个妻子再建立一个家庭?
Maybe.
也许吧
I can't believe you'veactually thought about this!
真不敢相信 你还真的想过这样的事情!
Haven't you?
你没想过吗?
Thought about who I'd marryif you died?
想过如果你死了我要嫁给谁?
Hmm. No.
没有
Well,honey,it's a back-upplan. I'm not gonna use it.
好了, 亲爱的, 这只是个下下策 我不会用的
Then why have it?
那为什么还要有呢?
Well,I don't know,because...
我不知道, 因为......
it's like,there's this door,right?
就像是, 这里有一扇门, 对吗?
And I'm not planning on actuallygoing through it
然后其实我并不打算穿过去
because I'm so happyin the room that I'm in.
因为我现在非常快乐 呆在现在的房间里
But in case of fire or flood,
但是如果房间起了火或者被洪水淹了
it's comforting to knowthat the door is unlocked.
然后得知房门没有锁 会让人感到很安慰的
Honey,I'm notthrough with that!
亲爱的, 我还没吃完那!
Yeah,well,why don't you have your second wifemake you lunch,okay? Oops!
好了, 为什么不让你的第二任老婆 来给你做午饭呢? 不好意思!
You...
你...
bree,uh,
Bree, 呃
I have to say,I was,uh,
我想说, 我, 呃
I was very pleasedto get your call.
非常高兴接到你的电话
I mean,I'm surprised you'd wantto have anything to do with me
我是说, 我很吃惊 你愿意和我出来谈谈
given our recent history.
评价一下我刚刚过去的历史
Oh,you mean your having suspected me of murdering my husband?
哦, 你是指你曾经怀疑 我谋杀了自己丈夫的事情?
Detective,that is allwater under the bridge now.
探长先生, 那件事情早已经过去了
I am very gladto hear you say that.
听你这样说我非常高兴
Although,I have to confess,I do have an ulterior motive.
但是, 我不得不承认 这次我确实另有所图
I need to ask you a favor.
我需要你帮我个忙
Oh,well,shoot,whatever I can do.
哦, 是吗, 请讲, 我尽力效劳
We have these,um,new neighbors-- the applewhites.
我们这里来了一个新邻居--- applewhite一家
It's a mother and her son. They just moved here from chicago.
一位母亲和她的儿子 他们刚从芝加哥搬来.
And they seem very nice. But there's--
他们看起来很友善 但是有些...
there's something about themthat'S...
有些他们的事情...
off.
不合常理
They're...
他们很...
odd.
古怪
Odd?
古怪?
Yeah,they're secretiveand watchful.
是的, 他们神神秘密的警惕性很高
And there was a dead bodyfound in front of their house.
而且在他们门前还发现了一具尸体
I can't run a background checkon your neighbors for being odd.
我是不能因为古怪 而去调查你邻居的背景的
Is that why youwanted to see me? To--
你想见我就是为这事? 让--
to ask me that?
让我调查这个?
Yeah,why?
是的, 怎么了?
Well,I just--during the investigation,
哦, 我以为--- 在调查你丈夫的案件期间
I just thought there wasa kind of a,um...
你我之间...
spark between us.
擦出了一些火花
You know,I thoughtthis might be a date.
我以为这次可能算是个约会
Uh,no.
哦, 不
I just wanted to ask you a favor.
我只是想请你帮个忙.
Fine,no harm done.
好的, 没什么
When do I ever getto have lunch with sucha lovely lady anyway?
既然能有幸邀请 如此可人的女士共进午餐
Date or...
约会或者...
no date.
不是约会
Are you sure that you can'tcheck on the applewhites?
你确定不能调查applewhite一家吗?
I mean,I just knowthat there's something there.
我的意思是, 我只感觉 有故事在里面
And,you know,I havea sixth sense about people.
知道吗, 我对人有一种第六感
And yet,you got engaged to the man who murdered your husband.
不一定, 你曾经和谋杀你丈夫的人定了婚
Well,your blood pressurelooks fine.
好了, 你的血压正常
You're free to go,mrs. Mayer.
你可以走了, mayer太太
You mean,I'm notgonna see dr. Ron?
你是说, 我不会去见Ron医生了?
Well,I do the follow-up exams.
是的, 由我来做以后的检查
Dr. Ron only comes inif there's a problem.
如果有问题, ron医生才会来.
Oh,well,maybe I shouldgo ahead and see him anyway,
哦, 好的, 也许我应该直接去找他
just to be safe.
只是为了安全起见.
I'm sorry.
对不起.
Dr. Ron's scheduleis very tight today.
今天Ron医生的安排非常紧.
So unless you'rehaving a serious problem...
除非你的情况很严重......
you're experiencing nausea, chills and tingling,huh?
你最近有恶心, 发冷及刺痛的症状, 是吗?
Yeah,
是的
but nowthat I think about it,
但是现在想想看
I bet it's justall the coffee I drink.
我肯定是喝的那些咖啡造成的.
I drink way too much coffee.
我喝了太多的咖啡.
Do you liketo drink coffee?
你喜欢喝咖啡吗?
Uh,no.No.
不, 不喜欢.
So the tingling is inyour fingers and your toes?
刺痛的感觉是出现在手指和脚趾上的吗?
I should switch to juice.I know the best juice place.
我应该改喝果汁了 我知道最好的果汁店在哪里.
You would love it.Do you drink juice?
你会喜欢的 你喝果汁吗?
Susan,how oftenhave you been having these involuntary muscle spasms?
Susan, 你这种不自觉的 肌肉痉挛现象多久会出现一次?
Oh,oh,not that often.
哦, 哦, 不是很频繁.
I probably just needa good massage.
我可能只是需要一次很好的按摩.
Susan?
Yeah?
怎么了?
I wanna get you infor an M.R.I.
我要给你做个核磁共振成像.
no,I don't thinkthat's necessary.
不, 没这个必要吧.
Are you a doctor?
你是医生吗?
I got high marksin math and science.
我以前数学和自然科学的成绩很好.
I wanna get you infor an M.R.I.
我要给你做个核磁共振成像.
No,no,no,I think giventhe misunderstanding
不, 不, 不, 我想一定是我让你误解了
that I should get the bill.
所以我来结帐单.
I won't hear of it.
我不会听的.
All right,
那好,
we'll split it.
我们分开付.
Fair enough.
很公平.
You know what?
我得说?
Let me,uh,let megive you a ride home.
我来, 我来开车送你回家吧.
Detective barton,is this somesort of high school ployto get me back to your place?
barton探长, 这不是要把我带回到你家的 这种高中生把戏吧?
I just don't thinkyou should be driving a car.You've been drinking.
我只是觉得你不应该再开车了 你一直在喝酒.
I had two glasses of wine.
我只喝了两杯.
Three,plus the tawny portwith dessert.
三杯, 外加一份焦制猪排.
It's all here on the bill
都清楚的写在帐单上
if you wanna take a look.
如果你要看一下的话.
You know what?
知道吗?
I politely rejected you,
我很礼貌的拒绝了你,
and now you're getting your revenge by embarrassing me.
而你现在却要找我难堪来报复.
You've had too much to drink. Give me your keys.
你不能再喝了 把车钥匙给我.
I am not giving you anything.
我什么都不会给你.
Except the bill.
除了这个帐单.
what do you thinkyou're doing?
你到底要干什么?
I followed you to make sureyou were okay.
我跟着你看看你是不是一切都好
You were weaving.
你驾车不太稳的样子
Please step outof the car.
请下车
Oh,you can't be serious.
哦,你不是认真的吧.
Out.
下来.
Detective,I am not drunk,and I am not stupid.
探长先生,我没有喝醉 而且我也不蠢
I know exactlywhat this is all about.
我知道这一切都是因为什么.
I'm gonna need you to takea sobriety test.
我需要带你去做一个酒精测试.
A sobriety test? I'm nottaking any sobriety...
酒精测试? 我不会去做任何的酒精...
test.
测试.
This behavior stems fromthe hurt feelings of a man withvery low self-esteem.
这是一种一个非常自卑的 男人在受到伤害时才会作出的行为.
The worldis a big place,
这个世界很大
and I'm sure there isa woman out there somewhere who'll respond to your
我肯定在某个地方一定有个女人 会喜欢你的这种
macho posturing.
男子气概.
Well...
好吧...
here's hoping.
Baby,what you're about to see
亲爱的,你将要看到的东西
will most likely shockand upset you.
会让你十分震惊和沮丧
Okay.
好吧.
Remember scott,the photographer I was dating when we met?
记得scott吗,那个我们遇见时 正和我约会的摄影师?
The one I dumped for you,
我就是为了你 才把他甩了
who never really got over it and who I always said
那个从来没有从感情中恢复过来 而我总是说他会来报复我的那个人?
was gonna get back at me?
他会来报复我的那个人?
Oh,carlos,I love you so much.
哦,carlos,我非常爱你
Move.
让开
What is this?
这是什么?
Scott's web site,
Scott的网页
with pictures of me on it.
上面有我的照片
well,say something.
好吧,说点什么
Oh,my god.
哦, 天哪
It wassupposed to be funny--
那本来只是用来好玩的--
a naughty little christmas gift for my boyfriend.
给我男朋友的圣诞小礼物
Oh,my god!
哦, 天哪
I know,I was freakishlyflexible back then.
我知道,我那时候 身体真是不可思议的柔软.
I'm sorry!
对不起!
Look,what are we gonna doabout this?
听着,我们需要做点什么吗?
I guessI'll call my lawyers.
我想我会打电话给我律师.
I gave these pictures to himas a gift. He owns them.
我把这些照片当作礼物送给他 这些是属于他的
Then I guesswe're screwed.
那么我想我们被敲诈了.
Not necessarily.
不一定.
See,here's what I'm thinking--
听着,我所想的是--
scott's a coward,
scott是个胆小鬼
so you could totallyput the scare into him.
你完全可以恐吓他.
All you gotta dois go and rough him up,
你所要做的就是去打他一顿
and he'll take my picturesoff the web site like that.
然后他就会像那样把我的照片 从那个网站上撤下来了
I'm sorry,but thisis your mistake.
我很抱歉,但这是你的过错
You're gonna have tofix it yourself.
你应该自己去解决它.
And I would love to,
我很想这么做
but I have the upper bodystrength of a kitten.
但我的力气最多只有一只小猫那样大
I need a brute!
我需要一个莽夫!!
Gaby,
Gaby
I am just now starting to get my rage issuesunder control.
我刚刚开始学会控制我的愤怒
This brute doesn't swingthat way anymore,
这个莽夫不会再像以前那样冲动了
so go find another.
所以去找别人吧
Well,when you left prison, did they leave youa contact list?
好吧,当你离开监狱时 他们有没有给你电话联系单?
So is dr. Ron gonnabe here for this?
Ron医生会来做这个是吗?
Oh,yeah,yeah,yeah.
哦,是的,是的
Uh,there's a hookon the wall there
嗯,墙上有挂钩
so go aheadand get your stuff hung up
把你的东西挂在上面
and,uh,just get comfy. Dr. Ronshould be here pretty soon.
还有,恩,放轻松一点 ron医生马上就来
Okay.Okay.
好的,好的
is she tryingto put on the dust cover?
她是不是在试着穿上 这个防尘罩?
yep.
是的.
How long are we gonna let this go on?
我们还要看着她这样多久?
Just a fewmore minutes.
再过一会就好
Hi,uh,susan?
嗨...susan?
It's dr. Ron.
我是ron医生
You don't have toget undressed for this.
你不用脱衣服的
Oh,uh,I-I,uh...
哦...我...
then why did youput out a gown?
那你们为什么放着睡袍?
No,no,it's not a gown.
不, 这不是睡袍?
It's the dust coverfor the M.R.I. Machine.
那是核磁共振机的防尘罩
This should takeabout 45 minutes.
这需要45分钟的时间
Now I know it's really crampedand uncomfortable in there,
我知道里面很挤也很不舒服
but try not to move.
但试着尽量不要移动
Susan,I realizethat this whole process must be troubling for you.
susan,我知道这整个过程让你很烦恼
Yeah,it's prettytroubling.
是,这真的很烦人
Well,we're gonna getto the bottom of this.
好吧,让我们完成这件事
And I'll be herefor you,okay?
我会在这里陪你,好吗?
Hey,dr. Ron?
嘿,ron医生?
I just have a feeling that everything'sgonna turn out fine.
我有一种感觉 我会好起来的
And when it does...
如果真是这样...
I'd like to buy you dinner
我想要请你共进晚餐
to celebrate my health.
为我的健康庆祝一下
You know,I was thinkingmaybe italian?
我想或许意大利菜?
Oh,what the heck,
哦,这真是
maybe we can call it a date.
或许我们可以称它为约会
If you like.
如果你想的话
Dr. Ron?
ron医生?
uh,he left awhile ago.
他几分钟前离开了
He got a phone callfrom his girlfriend.
他女朋友打电话来找他
Okay.
好吧.
Thank you.
谢谢你.
I'd liketo get out now.
我现在想要走了.
Try not to move.
尽量不要移动.
good morning,luis,ralph.
早上好,luis,ralph
-good morning,mrs. Solis.
-早上好,solis太太
good morning,mrs. Solis.
早上好,solis太太
Good morning,honey.
早上好 亲爱的
Hey,you're talkingto me again.
嘿 你又开始跟我说话了
Well,I thoughtabout what you said--
我仔细考虑了--
about the pictures--and you're right.
关于照片的事-- 你说得对
It was my mistake
是我自己的失误
and I have to live with it.
我得勇于面对
What the hellare you doing?!
你在干什么?
I'm living with it!
我要勇于面对!
Hey,turn aroundand keep gardening!
嘿 转过身去继续工作!
Aw,you're so mean.
哦 你真是刻薄
Put your clothes on right now.
马上穿上衣服
Why? You either careif men leer at me or not.
干嘛? 你到底在不在乎别人看我的身体?
And you made it clear thatyou don't. So what's the point?
你不是说你不在乎吗? 到底是什么意思?
Gabrielle,I am not beatingthis guy up for you!
Gabrielle 我不会为了你去揍那个家伙
Then you better think of anotherway to get my pictures back.
那你就能想个别的办法 把我的照片弄回来
Because if you don't,people on wisteria lane are gonna be seeinga lot more of me!
不然的话 我的身体就会 被整个紫藤街的居民一览无遗
Ralph,luis,feast your eyes!
Ralph Luis 一饱眼福吧!
My finger!
我的手指!
I'll find it!
我找找!
Aah,my finger!
哦 我的手指!
It's gotta be here somewhere.
肯定就在这附近
I'll look for it,man.
我这就找 兄弟
Don't worry,man.
别担心
-I'll find it.Oh,
- 我会找到的
my finger!
我的手指!
Hey,honey,
嘿 亲爱的
good news.
好消息
I checked on penny,
我去看Penny
and she didn't scream.
她居然没有尖叫
I think she's getting usedto the mask.
可能她已经习惯我这个面具了
I don't want youto have options,tom.
我不要你有选择余地 Tom
If I die,I wanna hearyour life would be over.
你告诉我 如果我死了 你会从此失去幸福
I want you to spendthe rest of your life screaming,
我要你的余生都在尖叫嚎哭中度过
"it should've been meon that plane!"
"为什么在飞机上的不是我!"
-Plane?
- 飞机?
I'm assuming there was a crash.
假设我是飞机失事遇难
It could've been something else.
当然也可能是别的情况
Okay,wait,wait,wait,wait.
好 等等...
Do you have any idea
你到底能不能了解
how painful it is to hear about you even thinkabout your next wife and kids?
听到你在考虑下任妻子和小孩的时候 我有多痛苦
I could never do that!
我绝不会做这种事
I can't imagine my lifewithout you.
我无法想象没有你的生活
You are my everything!
你就是我的一切
Honey,you're my everything.
亲爱的 你也是我的一切
Okay,well,that's easy to say,
好了 说说倒容易
but I need youto show me.
但我要你证明给我看
How?
怎么证明?
With a vasec to me.
做精管切除手术
Can't I justget you some flowers?
能不能送花给你就算了?
Look,it makesperfect sense.
这完全合理
We're not gonna haveany more kids.
我们不会再生小孩了
And the pill just makesme bloat. It'll be great!
避孕药会让我发胖 做了手术就好了!
No,okay,lynette,
好了 Lynette
this is crazy.
太胡闹了
Oh,I know! I know!
哦 我知道 我知道!
But it is whatmarried people do.
不过恩爱夫妻就该这样
They go out of their way to calmeach other's irrational fears.
为了安抚对方不理智的恐惧 而不惜一切代价
Oh,come on,tom.
哦 拜托 Tom
I really need youto do this.
你就帮帮我嘛
Well,okay.
那好吧
Fine,yeah.
我答应你
I'll make an appointment.
我会去预约
Thank you.
谢谢你
can I ask yousomethin'?
我能问你些事情吗?
I'd rather you didn'T.
你不是已经在问了?
How'd you get started?
你是怎么开始的?
-Started?
- 开始?
You know,
那个嘛
in the escort business?
开始出来做应召女?
I beg your pardon.
有没有搞错
I bet the guys go crazywith your whole...
男人肯定为你神魂颠倒...
classy,repressed thingyou got going on,huh?
喜欢你玩优雅 扮矜持 对吧?
I mean,your skin has,like, no pores.
看你的皮肤 又细又嫩
I am not sure,but I think there wasa compliment in there somewhere,
我不太确定 不过你的话里似乎还有称赞的意味
so thank you.
所以先谢谢了
But I am not an escort.
不过我不是应召女郎
How much you chargea night?
你一晚上收费多少?
Look,I'M...
听着 我...
$5,000.
$5,000
What do you have to doexactly for 5 grand?
这5千块到底包括哪些服务?
All right.
好了
Your bail cleared.You're free to go.
你获保释 可以走了
Your car'sat the impound lot.
你的车暂时扣押
And you can pick it upin the morning.
早上再来取
Well,how am I supposed to get home? I don't have any money.
那我怎么回家? 我身无分文
Call a friend.
叫朋友
I have been through enoughhumiliation for one day.
我今天受够了羞辱
I hope you have a bettersuggestion than that.
我希望你有更好的建议
Okay,well,let me think,um...
好吧 那我想想...
walk.
走回去
oh,for goodness sakes!
哦 真是的!
bree?
Bree?
Is everything okay?
还好吧?
Oh,oh,I'm fine.I just,um,had a flat tire.
哦 没事 只是车胎没气了
It's your lucky day.
今天算你走运
I'm a whizat changing tires. Hop in.
换车胎是我的强项 进来吧
You know,thank you,
谢谢你的好意
but I think it's actuallysomething more mechanical.
不过 应该不只是换车胎这么简单
My car has been makingjust a terrible noise.
我的车甚至发出奇怪声响
Well,I have auto club.
没问题的 我参加了一个汽车俱乐部
Come on.
来吧
Actually,
实际上
my car has beenimpounded by the police.
我的车被警察扣押了
Thanks,betty,and,um...
多谢,betty,嗯
I'd appreciate itif you could keep this little incidentto yourself.
如果你能不对任何人提起这件事 我将感激不尽
I won't say a word.I swear.
我不会说半个字,我保证
Well,that's good to hear,
这话耐听
because most people on thisstreet couldn't keep a secret
因为住在这条街上的人 不可能守得主秘密
if their lives depended on it.
当搬弄是非就是他们 生活的一部分
Well,bree,
那,bree
even if everyone does find out,
就算每个人知道了
it's no big deal.
有何关系
I mean,lots of peoplehave D.U.I.S.
很多人都有酒后驾车的经历
Yes,but the difference ismost of those people were actually drunkwhen they were arrested.
话是没错 区别就在于那些人的确喝醉了
I was not.
但我没有
Well,of course.
当然
You know,you sound likeyou don't believe me.
你的口气就像不相信我
Well,um,it's just...
恩,只是...
I know you've gone througha lot lately--
我明白你最近经历太多事
the death of your husband,problems with your son.
你丈夫的去世,你儿子的问题
It would only be naturalif you did self-medicate.
就算你在偷偷服药也在情理之中
I'm sorry,but sincewhen do you know so much aboutmy personal life?
抱歉,从什么时候你对我的私生活 如此了解
Bree,
Bree
it's like you said--
就像你说的
the people on this street arenot great at keeping secrets.
那条街上的人不擅长保守秘密
Except for you.
除你之外
You're reallygood at it.
你真的很厉害
I beg your pardon.
你说什么
Well,you moved into your housein the middle of the night.
你当初半夜三更才动手搬家
God knowswhat you moved in that you didn't wantanybody to see.
天晓得你有什么见不得人的东西
People hear soundscoming at all hours from there.
随时都能听到房子里 发出奇怪的声音
And,oh,what was the last one?Oh,right--
噢,上次是怎么回事？ 噢,没错
they found a dead bodyin front of your home.
他们在你家门口发现一具尸体
Everybody talks aboutthe applewhites,
所有人都在议论Applewhites
but nobody can figure out exactly what you peopleare hiding.
但没人知道你们究竟 在隐瞒些什么
So congratulations.
那么恭喜
Your secrets are safe...
你的秘密安然无恙
for now.
目前而已
Edie?
Hi,it's betty applewhite.
我是Betty Applewhite
Yeah,I'm sorryto call you so late but,um...
抱歉这么晚还来打扰你 但...
I really need to meet with youfirst thing in the morning.
但明儿一大早能碰面吗？
Yes.
没错
Well,I've decidedto sell my house.
我决定把房子卖了
Dr. Ron?
Ron医生
What are you doing here?
你来干什么？
Uh,we need to talk.
我们需要谈谈
And it's not the kind of talkwe can have over the phone.
电话上讲不清
Oh,are you sure?
噢,你确定吗？
Um,becauseI would look a lot better over the phone right now.
因为电话上的我不会这么邋遢
Um,susan,your,uh,your test results came back.
Susan,你的化验结果拿到了
And for the life of me,I can't figure it out.
根据我的经验,我无法判定
Now based on the--on the symptoms you were describing--
目前根据你描述的那些症状...
symptoms?
症状
Yeah,the dizziness,the tingling, the muscle spasms,
头晕眼花,麻木,肌肉痉挛
the chills--it could be neurological.
打寒战,也可能是神经问题
It also could be basedon an autoimmune disorder.
也可能是免疫系统紊乱
I just--frankly,I'm stumped.
我只是...坦白讲,毫无头绪
Oh,no,no,no,no.
不不不不
Hey,listen,we're gonnaget through this,okay?
听着,我们会找到症结,明白吗？
I am so sorry.
我真的很抱歉
But I'm not sick.
但我没病
What are youtalking about?
你什么意思？
your nurse wouldn'tlet me see you,and I...
你的护士不让我见你,所以我
really wanted to see you,
真的想见你一面
so I sort of fakedall my symptoms.
于是我假装有那些症状
The dizziness,the chills,you know, all of it.
头晕眼花,寒战,一切的一切
Why--why would youdo something like that?
为什么你要这么做？
What the hellis wrong with you?
你究竟搞什么名堂？
I know. I know.I feel really awful.
我知道,我知道,真对不住
I am just not the bestat meeting men.
我只是不擅长面对男士
And I thought you were cute,
我对你有感觉
and I sort of thought that maybe you thoughtI was cute,
然后我开始胡思乱想 也许你也对我又感觉
and you're a doctor,and that's so sexy.
而且你又是个医生 那真让人兴奋
So I was up all nightworried sick
这么说我一晚上没睡觉 为你的病担忧
digging through medical books,
遍阅医学文献
trying to figure outsome mysterious disease that doesn't really exist?
尽全力查明一种神秘的疾病 结果根本不存在？
Really?You were up all night?
真的？你一夜没睡？
Yes.
没错
I don't enjoytelling people I thinkthey're going to die.
我不喜欢对一个人说 "你时日不多"的话
Especially not people I like.
尤其是我喜欢的人
You like me?
你喜欢我？
Yes.
没错
What about your girlfriend?
那你的女友呢？
-What girlfriend?
- 什么女友？
The one who calledin the M.R.I. Room?
那个打电话到检查室来的？
We had one date. She wanteda referral to a dermatologist.
我们约会过一次,她想让我帮 她推荐一个皮肤科医生
She's got eczema.
她换了湿疹
Maybe we couldgo out sometime?
也许下次我们可以一块出去？
Do you like sushi?
你喜欢寿司吗？
I love sushi.
我爱吃寿司
I'm available tomorrow night.
明晚就有空
No,no,no,tomorrow's no good. I'll still be angry.
不不,明天不行,我还在气头上
I should be cooled downby friday.
到星期五就没事了
Oh,uh,friday's good.
星期五不错
Oh,there's one thing--
噢,还有件事
your M.R.I. Showed that you havea wandering spleen.
你的扫描结果显示 你有个游动的脾脏
A what?
一个什么？
It's a wandering spleen. It's no big deal.
游动的脾脏 并无大碍
Sometimes the thing just moves around in there.
有时那些玩意儿会游来游去
But we'll keepan eye on it.
但我们会留心注意
Wandering what?
游动的什么？
Okay,
好吧
go get him,tiger.
去给他点教训,猛男
I can't do it,gaby.
我办不到,Gaby
What?
什么？
I can't go in there.I thought I could, but I can'T.
我无法进去,我以为我可以 但实我就是办不到
You promised!
你向我保证过
Ever since I got outof prison,
自从我从牢房里出来
I've been tryingto lead a better life.
我一直在努力好好过日子
And for the first time,I can honestly say
而这是头一次 我可以问心无愧的说
that I'm a good catholic, and I don't want to ruin that.
我是一个善良天主教徒 我不想毁掉它
So do this today and go toan extra long mass tomorrow.
明天做一个超长的弥撒 主就会原谅你了
It doesn't workthat way.
那没有用
Okay,
好吧
look,I'm really trying to understandyour moral dilemma here,I am.
我真的理解你良心的挣扎 真的
But if you don't getmy pictures back,
但如果你不去把我的照片拿回来
I'm gonna be humiliated.
我会没脸见人
You think our gardener is the only local pervsurfing the web?
你认为这附近只有我们家园丁 那两个变态？
I'm sorry,gabrielle.
抱歉,Gabrielle
You used to go crazy
你以前会火冒三丈
when men would so muchas look at me the wrong way--
一遇到其他男人多看我两眼
and that's whenI had clothes on.
而且我还没有裸露
I'm trying to bebetter than that now.
我现在想用更好的办法
Or maybe you just don't love meas much as you used to.
或者也许是你不再像以前那样 爱我
Why can't you just let mebe a good person?
你为什么就不能让我做一个好人？
You know,if you really loved me,
如果你真的爱我
you wouldn't even ask meto go in there.
你就不会逼我去那里
If you really loved me, I wouldn't have to ask!
如果你真的爱我 我也不需要这么逼你
fine,forget it.
好吧,算了
Really?
真的？
Be a good person.
成全你当好人
Knock yourself out.
不必客气
It's not thatI don't love you. I--
不是我不爱你
yeah,okay,look,let's just go home.
好吧,听着,回家去
What are you doing?
你干什么？
I'm gettingyour pictures back.
我去把你的照片拿回来
I'm not gonna hurt him.
我不会伤害他
I'll talk to him,
我去劝他
appeal to his better nature.
劝他良心发现
Can I help you?
有何贵干？
I'm carlos solis.
我是Carlos Solis
You have,uh,naked picturesof my wife on your web site.
你的网站上有我妻子的裸照
You're,uh...
你是...
gabrielle's husband?
Gabrielle的丈夫？
well,you know what? I was just aboutto take those off anyway.
你知道吗？ 我正打算把它们拿掉
That's great.
那就好
I reallyappreciate this,scott.
我万分感激,Scott
Hey,no problem.
嘿,小事一桩
To tell you the truth,gabrielle's pages weren't exactly raking inthe big bucks for me.
实话实说,Gabrielle的网页 没为我赚到大钱
I find thathard to believe.
我难以相信
I'm not saying gabrielle's nota pretty girl.
不是说Gabrielle长的不漂亮
Of course she is.But,uh,
她当然漂亮,但
she ain't exactlyinternet pretty,you know?
她在网上不太受欢迎,你知道吗？
What does that mean?
那是什么意思？
The web's about fantasy,not fashion.
这些网站提供幻想而不是时尚
I mean,guys surfingfor porn,
那些家伙需要的是色情
they don't care how the clothesare hanging off the body.
他们才不在乎怎么脱衣服
They just wanna seethe goods. So,uh,
他们只想看好玩意儿
if little miss nastyain't rocking some curves...
要是小辣妹没有真材实料
my wife has a perfect figure.
我妻子有完美曲线
Don't get me wrong.
别误会
Our little gaby knows how to,uh...
我们可爱的Gaby懂得如何
work a runway,but,uh,
摆造型
when it comesto cyber lovin'?
但这是在网上
No real man's gonnawaste tissue on that. There you go.
没人会在那些东西上浪费精力 给你
That's all of 'em.
全部
So we cool now?
我们没事了？
now that's my guy.
这才是我的男人
You're not limping.
你好像没有无精打采
Did everything go okay?
一切可好？
I couldn't do it.
我办不到
What happened?
发生了什么？
I don't know. I got there,I...
我不知道,我到了那里...
I put on the paper gownand I,uh...
换上手术服,然后我
I just couldn't do it.
我就是办不到
Why not?
为什么？
It felt likeI was being emasculated.
感觉就像被阉割了
Oh,please.
拜托
I'm serious,lynette.
我说真的,Lynette
I don't make the moneyaround here anymore.
我不再挣钱
I don't providefor you and the kids.
不再养家糊口
And I wasn't go
我不会让他们剪掉唯一能让自己感觉 像个男人的东西
And i wasn't going to  let them snip out the l ast thing that make me feel a man
Staying  home and taking care of the kids doesn't make you less of a man
当家庭主男不会有损你的男子气概
that's crazy
别胡思乱想
you expect me to calm your rational fears,
你指望我安抚你不理智的恐惧，
i expect you  to calm mine
我同样指望着你,
Are you saying you are not happy ?
你的意思是你过得不快乐？
A little bit yeah
有一点
Well what we gonna do about that ?
那我们怎么办？
i don't know
我不知道
-can we just ?
-我们能不能就...?
no,Lynette
不行,Lynette
I don't know
我不知道
hi,it's detective barton,look i feel awful about what happend the other day,
我是Barton警探,听我说, 我为那天发生的事道歉,
I was the jerk
我是个混蛋
so to make it up to you
为了补偿你
I did some sniffing around about the dead man
我查了一下
they found in front of your neigbours house
在你邻居家门前发现那 死者的底细
I got some information his name is Curt Monroe
我得到一些资料他叫Curt Monroe
A private detective who lost his license a couple years ago
一位几年前就被吊销执照的私家侦探
Apparently he is from Chicago
显然他来自芝加哥
I don't if this is helpful but...
我不知道这会不会有帮助但
years ago,he is apparently from Chicago
几年前,显然他来自芝加哥
I,I don't know if this is helpful but
我不知道这会不会有帮助  但......
I just feel terrible about what happened
我的确为那天的事难过
illness can take on many  forms
疾病有很多种表现方式
those of the body are easy to treat
身体上的容易治疗
Much more difficult
困难的是,
are the hidden maladies festering in our hearts
隐埋在内心深处的伤痛
the secret diction that consume our soul
不为人知的迷恋让我们的灵魂中毒
and the disease  we deny
讳疾忌医
which affect our judgement
会困惑我们的判断
To survive we need to find that special someone who can heal us
为了继续下去,我们得找到一位能 帮助我们痊愈的人
I work so hard on my life,
我一生如此努力,
so hard
如此努力
Now it's all nothing
现在却一无所有
i got one daughter i hate who hates me
我从来就没疼爱过她
before her time
在她出生前一天
No one left for me now
现在这世上已经没人值得我留念
What did I do it for
我这都是何苦
it was good i
不错,
did't feel a thing
我一点感觉也没有
XXXXX
没关系
XXXXXXXX
反正我已失去感觉
But we can never predict
但我们永远也不会料到
who have the cure for what ills us
谁会有我们的解药
or when  they'll show up
或者什么时候他们会出现
But I think we can get along,
但我们会相处愉快
just
放心吧